Contact

6361563076 (Mobile) pranavms13@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/pranavms13 (LinkedIn) pranavms.ml (Personal)

Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)
MERN Stack
Android Development

Languages

Kannada (Native or Bilingual)
Hindi (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Microsoft Technology Associate (MTA) Python

Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter tuning, Regularization and Optimization

Front-End Web UI Frameworks and Tools: Bootstrap 4

C++ Course

Machine Learning

Honors-Awards

Winner of HackBout 2.0

Pranav M S

Student

Bangalore Urban

Summary

I grew up in Bangalore, India.

Currently pursuing Computer Science Engineering in K S Institute of Technology. AlsoInterested in Developing applications. I started coding at the age of 10. Started many hobby projects and later worked as a Lead Developer for a Proof-Of-Work Based Cryptocurrency "ReCoal".

My interests also include Web Development, Mobile App Development, IoT Based Automation and Penetration Testing.

Experience

Scholarly Science
Full Stack Developer
August 2020 - September 2020 (2 months)

Bengaluru South Education and Social Transformation Web Developer

January 2020 - March 2020 (3 months)

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Kaggle

Competition Contributer
October 2019 - March 2020 (6 months)

Verzeo

ML Developer July 2019 - August 2019 (2 months) Bengaluru Area, India

Completed Internship at Verzeo.

Education

KS Institute Of Technology

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Science · (2018 - 2022)